<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[The House of Cheese]]></title>
  <link href="http://ilovecheese.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ilovecheese.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-12T15:54:12-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://ilovecheese.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Cheesemaster]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Tinker With SDR]]></title>
    <link href="http://ilovecheese.github.io/blog/2014/02/12/first-tinker-with-sdr/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-12T15:51:19-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://ilovecheese.github.io/blog/2014/02/12/first-tinker-with-sdr</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Well I have been interested in HAM radio for years now and have been talking about getting hardware and my liscense.
Recently I read <a href="http://blog.cyberexplorer.me/2014/01/sniffing-and-decoding-nrf24l01-and.html">sniffing-and-decoding-nrf24l01</a>.
Figured this would get me back motivated for getting my license. I also found a cool application for tracking airplanes on <a href="http://youtu.be/HS38q3YXsY4">Hak5</a>.
Have not tried the airplane one yet. The dongle that I ordered is not good quality, it requires me to hold pressure on the USB or it disconnects. I have a different one in route now. I also bought a antenna. More details on that later. If it does not work well I&rsquo;ll make my own. I have not had the best of luck running SDR# in mono in Linux yet (think it&rsquo;s from the random kernel detaches from the crappy design). Looking after I get licensed about getting a upconverter and just using a SDR setup on the HAM bands.</p>

<p><em>Tootles for now!</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Octopress]]></title>
    <link href="http://ilovecheese.github.io/blog/2014/02/08/octopress/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-08T11:19:25-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://ilovecheese.github.io/blog/2014/02/08/octopress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This looks like it is <em>much</em> better than Wordpress. Also I&rsquo;ve now got my feet wet with <a href="www.github.com">Git</a> and <a href="www.ruby-lang.org">Ruby</a>.
Trying to write in Markdown failed me at first, had trouble finding software or gedit plugins. Looks like a lot of people use Vi (will tackle that later).
Currently I&rsquo;m using Eclipse with a Markdown plugin. Ruby is really fascinating to me how all the gems work. Makes me miss coding and the trill when it works as attended.
While I was in middle school I spent a lot of time in VB3 writing applications for a popular online software.
I like how <a href="www.codeacademy.com">codeacademy</a> is setup perhaps that&rsquo;s one of my next adventures.</p>

<p><strong>More later, have a good day</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
